Guide to the Henry H. Jones Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2007-052
  - Restricted Material:
    - Radiology 237 10 Feb. '96 Grading (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Radiology 237 General Info. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - #237 5 Feb. '94 Completed Sign-in Sheets (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Radiology #237 – Student Signups for Seminars – 5 Feb '94 course (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Radiology #237 Signups 9 Jan ‘93 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Test Case 1: Isolated rotatory subluxation of the scaphoid (Carpal Navicular) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Test Case 4: Blow-out fracture of the orbit (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Test Case 5: Complete rotator cuff tear (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Test Case 6: Rupture of the tibiofibular ligament (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Test Case 7: Eversion Injury with Rupture of the Tibiofibular Ligament (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Test Case 8: Tear of the medial meniscus (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Test Case 9: Inversion Injury (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Test Case 10: (Volar) Lunate Dislocation (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Test Case 11: Posterior dislocation of the humeral head (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Test Case 12: Posterior Mediastinal Hematoma Associated with Multiple Thoracic Vertebral Body Fractures (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Normals: - Case 23: Shoulder – Test Case 2: Great Trochanter/Neck of femur – Test Case 3: Angle of Mandible (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Dr. Henry Jones Bone Path. Teaching File 1976-8 A thru G (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Dr. Henry Jones Bone Path. Teaching File 1976-8 H thru P (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Teaching Cases – Lists to be Worked Over (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Elbow Project-Magnification Calculations (Box 19, Folder 21)